[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110724pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 10, "question": "Were you a good hog slayer?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 11, "answer": "I was.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110724pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "CC", "PRP$", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 36, "question": "What does that mean?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 37, "answer": "Well, I tell a lot of stories in my standup act that, you know, or my points of view of different things.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110724pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 42, "question": "To put it mildly, haven't you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["TO", "VB", "PRP", "RB", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 43, "answer": "Well, I think if you do standup, the kind of standup I like, you've got to tell the truth and you know hopefully you've had some interesting things.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110724pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 53, "question": "Is there anything about your life that you can't joke about?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "EX", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 54, "answer": "Well, I can't think of anything.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110724pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NN", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", ":", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 85, "question": "Your weight, the way you look, everything?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 86, "answer": "My battle with food and my weight is the core of every -- of my alcoholism, of everything.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110724pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 89, "question": "And how are you feeling these days about the way you look?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 90, "answer": "I need to lose some weight.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Hormel"]}, "docId": "110724pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "NNP", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 102, "question": "Did you remember that experience well?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 103, "answer": "I remember working at Hormel very well.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110724pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 114, "question": "Were you a good hog slayer?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 115, "answer": "I was.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110724pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 121, "question": "Were they eating a bacon sandwich at the time, don't they?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 122, "answer": "Absolutely.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110724pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 127, "question": "In what way?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 128, "answer": "I mean, they are animals.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110724pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 129, "question": "Do you feel guilty?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 130, "answer": "Probably.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Hormel"]}, "docId": "110724pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 133, "question": "Do you ever wonder if your life hadn't taken a deviation in standup, do you ever wonder if you could -- if you were still there now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "JJR", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "JJR", "IN", "PRP", "MD", ":", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 134, "answer": "You know, when I don't feel -- you know, I got fired from Hormel.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110724pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", ":", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", ":"], "qSentId": 136, "question": "What?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "."], "aSentId": 137, "answer": "So -- yes, it was first --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mike"], "LOCATION": ["Ottumwa", "Iowa"]}, "docId": "110724pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", ",", "NNP", ",", "CC", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBP", "RB", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "TO", "DT", "NN", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NNP", ",", "NNP", ",", "IN", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 143, "question": "You did what?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "WP", "."], "aSentId": 144, "answer": "Well, me, Mike, and Mo, who are still buddies of mine to this day, there's nothing to do in Ottumwa, Iowa, after 10:00.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110724pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "."], "qSentId": 159, "question": "What was that moment like?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 160, "answer": "Terrifying.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"MONEY": ["$15"], "LOCATION": ["University of Iowa"]}, "docId": "110724pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "$", "CD", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 178, "question": "When was the moment that you realized this could be a career, and not just a bit of fun for you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "RB", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 179, "answer": "The first time I got offered a paying job, $15, I was in University of Iowa and I had some standup.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110724pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "CC", "NNS", "VBP", "TO", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "TO", "PRP$", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "RB", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 193, "question": "I mean, is that a good thing or not a good thing for you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 194, "answer": "You know, but people have to understand, I haven't talked to her, you know, face to face in almost 18 years.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110724pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 198, "question": "Do you ever?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 199, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110724pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 202, "question": "Do you follow her on Twitter?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP$", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 203, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["1983"]}, "docId": "110724pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 234, "question": "But I would imagine for a while, it must have been electrifying, wasn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "VBG", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 235, "answer": "Well, it was great fun because we met in 1983.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110724pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 250, "question": "Did any part of you missing that kind of chaotic exciting, you're center stage?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 251, "answer": "Oh, I'm sure the alcoholic part of me, the self-destructive part of me misses it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110724pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 263, "question": "When you go to a newsstand, do you ever have a little thought (ph) of, oh, I wish they were putting me on the cover again?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "DT", "RB", "VBN", "-NONE-", "NN", ":", "IN", ",", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 264, "answer": "Like I say, there's that voice inside of me, it's not a happy voice that does.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110724pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 288, "question": "And what would you say to her if she's watching?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "PRP$", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 289, "answer": "I'd say good luck with your show.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110724pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "IN", "PRP$", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 293, "question": "Do you think she'll be pleased that you're happy?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 294, "answer": "Part of her, no.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110724pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 324, "question": "Rather impressive remarks there I think, Tom, to your old friend Arnold Schwarzenegger?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "JJ", "NNS", "EX", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", ",", "TO", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 325, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Arnold Schwarzenegger"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Austria"]}, "docId": "110724pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "IN", "DT", ":", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", ":", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 338, "question": "What do you make of what's been going on?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "WP", "POS", "VBN", "VBG", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 339, "answer": "Well, you have to understand he grew up in a -- much like me in a small town in -- in Austria in his case.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110724pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 349, "question": "Were you -- were you as shocked as everybody else?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", ":", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 350, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110724pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 359, "question": "About what's been going on?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "POS", "VBN", "VBG", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 360, "answer": "Well, we see each other.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110724pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "RBR", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 365, "question": "At what point can you crack a joke about this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "NN", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 366, "answer": "Well, the only joke that I can crack is that he can no longer make fun of the women that I've been with.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110724pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 379, "question": "But to him personally, just as a guy, a friend of yours, how is he dealing with it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "TO", "PRP", "RB", ",", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", ",", "WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 380, "answer": "He's always been tough about that stuff.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110724pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 391, "question": "Is that a go, or is it -- but might that happen?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "VBZ", "PRP", ":", "CC", "MD", "IN", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 392, "answer": "I think it's a go.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110724pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 396, "question": "You've been talking about it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 397, "answer": "Absolutely, we've been talking about it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Arnold"]}, "docId": "110724pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 406, "question": "The -- what kind of man is Arnold Schwarzenegger?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", ":", "WP", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBZ", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 407, "answer": "I think Arnold is a great man.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Arnold Schwarzenegger"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110724pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 422, "question": "You think he has physical aspirations or is that pretty well dead in the water, do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "NNS", "CC", "VBZ", "IN", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 423, "answer": "I don't know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110724pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 431, "question": "Do you feel because of that, because politics has now been shut down really for him, that the movies, which is what propelled him really into the stratosphere, that that may be the love again for him, that he may just go back to that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "IN", "DT", ",", "IN", "NNS", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "VBN", "RP", "RB", "IN", "PRP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", "WP", "VBN", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", ",", "IN", "DT", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "RB", "IN", "PRP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "RB", "TO", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 432, "answer": "Absolutely.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110724pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 448, "question": "I mean, it's like a -- it's a torturous process, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 449, "answer": "It is torturous, and it's monotonous.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110724pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 459, "question": "You've made 100 movies?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "CD", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 460, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110724pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "``", "JJ", "NNS", "''", ":"], "qSentId": 461, "question": "Which is your favorite?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WDT", "VBZ", "PRP$", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 462, "answer": "Well, I mean, I loved \"True Lies\" --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110724pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBD", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 473, "question": "The one you don't like to talk about in civilized company?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "CD", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 474, "answer": "I think there was one.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110724pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "DT", "NN", ":"], "qSentId": 527, "question": "-- at your worst, what are we talking in terms of consumption?", "question_pos_tagged": [":", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 528, "answer": "I was about a half ounce a day --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110724pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": [":", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 529, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 530, "answer": "-- of cocaine.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110724pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 534, "question": "Did you remember how that made you feel?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "WRB", "IN", "VBN", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 535, "answer": "Well, I will tell you this.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110724pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 545, "question": "Do you -- do you drink at all now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", ":", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 546, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110724pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "qSentId": 548, "question": "Literally nothing at all?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 549, "answer": "Nothing.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110724pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "RB", ",", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 550, "question": "And do you ever get tempted?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 551, "answer": "I watch people sometimes, normal people.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110724pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "NNS", "CC", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 567, "question": "Did you have any regrets about it, or is it something that happened to you, that you're just pleased you moved on that was for a long time probably quite a bit fun?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", ",", "CC", "VBZ", "PRP", "NN", "WDT", "VBD", "TO", "PRP", ",", "DT", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "RB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 568, "answer": "RNOLD: I have regrets about the way I acted, you know, when I was using drugs and alcohol.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110724pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NNS", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "CD", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NN", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 577, "question": "How much of what went on then do you think determined how you became in your earlier adulthood?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "IN", "WP", "NN", "IN", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP$", "JJR", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 578, "answer": "Well, relationships-wise, if your mom leaves when you're four, you know, anything is possible.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110724pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNS", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 591, "question": "What happened to the abuser?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 592, "answer": "Well, after I got sober, you know, you -- you spin through things, and you work on things.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110724pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", ":", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 617, "question": "What did you do?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 618, "answer": "I just -- I just said what I had to say.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110724pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 639, "question": "Did you hit him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 640, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110724pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 662, "question": "And did it bring you any kind of closure?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBD", "PRP", "VBG", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 663, "answer": "Absolutely.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110724pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJS", "NN", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 712, "question": "Who gave it to you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 713, "answer": "The best advice was to make it the priority of my day every day above my relationship witness, above my career.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110724pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 719, "question": "And who gave you that advice?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 720, "answer": "Well, I got a lot of advice.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Charlie"]}, "docId": "110724pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 728, "question": "When you see someone like Charlie going through what he's been through the last few months, what's been your -- your view watching from afar?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "VBG", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "PRP$", ":", "PRP$", "NN", "VBG", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 729, "answer": "Well, you know, I love Charlie.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Charlie"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110724pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", ":", "IN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 754, "question": "I mean, there in a nutshell is the immorality of Hollywood, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "EX", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 755, "answer": "That's the immorality of -- of everywhere.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Hollywood"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110724pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ":", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 773, "question": "What in the end made you stop?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 774, "answer": "I -- there was a night.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110724pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 805, "question": "Does he have anyone around him that can give him that hug?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 806, "answer": "You know, he's lost a lot this year.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110724pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 825, "question": "What did you think of that decision?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 826, "answer": "I think Ashton would be great.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110724pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "VBG", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 865, "question": "Have you managed to, despite all the partying and the extravagances and so on, have you retained enough to be pretty comfortable the rest of your life?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", ",", "IN", "DT", "DT", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NNS", "CC", "RB", "IN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VBN", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 866, "answer": "Well, if I'd have continued partying, obviously, I wouldn't have anything.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110724pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "PRP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 885, "question": "Money?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "aSentId": 886, "answer": "Security has brought me happiness.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110724pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 929, "question": "Is that something that you'd like to do now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 930, "answer": "Yes, we'd like to do that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110724pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 934, "question": "Do you think you'd be a good father?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 935, "answer": "I hope so, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110724pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", ":", "NNS", "VBP", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "NNP", "NNP", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", ",", "VB", "NN", "IN", "NN", "RB", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", "VBG", "NN", "CC", "RB", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "JJ", ",", "IN", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 946, "question": "Who makes you laugh out loud?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 947, "answer": "You know, I liked -- sounds crazy but I liked Bob Hope a lot when I first moved out here because my dad used to laugh at him, get home from work late and I could hear him and my dad howling laughing and so, when I got to a Bob Hope special, that was a big thing.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110724pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 951, "question": "Is he the guy that all stand-ups revere?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 952, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110724pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["."], "qSentId": 954, "question": "He is, you know?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 955, "answer": ".", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110724pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "JJS", "NN", ",", "IN", "NN", "NN", ",", "IN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "JJ", "NNS", "WDT", "VBD", "TO", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 956, "question": "Why was he so special?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 957, "answer": "Because he dealt with the harshest stuff, with drug addiction, with -- you know, horrible injuries that happened to him.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Dax Sheppard", "Bradley Cooper"], "LOCATION": ["America"]}, "docId": "110724pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "WDT", ":", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "RB", "VBZ", "VBG", ",", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "NN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "CC", "VBG", ":", "NN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 960, "question": "What are you working on?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 961, "answer": "I'm Just finishing a movie that -- Dax Sheppard, who is the funniest man in America now is directing, with Bradley Cooper, as I said, playing a bad guy, and working -- movie stuff, I'm on the road.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110724pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 968, "question": "And you're also involved in independent films, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 969, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110724pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "RBR", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", ":"], "qSentId": 974, "question": "Given your often outrageous life, if I could give you five minutes to relive one moment in your life and it couldn't be wives or children, what would it be?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP$", "RB", "JJ", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "CD", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "CD", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "NNS", "CC", "NNS", ",", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 975, "answer": "I would probably be more careful with my career in the '90s, you know, instead of taking a lot of things --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Ashley"]}, "docId": "110724pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 984, "question": "The single greatest thing, do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 985, "answer": "I would say -- I don't mean to sound cliche but my marriage to Ashley, because I quit the marriage thing.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]